redirect.com 2019-06-12

# Redirect.com

_Published: June 26, 2018_

We recognize the importance of protecting the privacy of your personal information, and we have prepared this Privacy Policy to provide you with important information about our privacy practices. This Privacy Policy applies when you use a website, mobile or tablet application, or other online service (collectively, the "Services") that links or refers to it. 

**If you are a user in the European Economic Area** ("EEA") or Switzerland, please see the **Users in the EEA and Switzerland** section of this Privacy Policy for additional provisions that are applicable to your use of the Services. 

**_Information We Collect_**

We may collect personal information about our users in various ways. For example, we may collect information that you provide to us, information that we collect through your use of the Services, and information that we collect from publicly available sources or third parties. 

**Information You Provide to Us.** When you register or otherwise interact with the Services, you may be invited to provide personal information to enhance your experience on the Services. For example, during account registration, we may ask for information such as your name, e-mail address, year of birth, gender, street address, job title and industry and related information. We may collect payment information, such as your credit card number and expiration date, where appropriate to process a financial transaction you have requested. 

We also collect information that you provide us when you comment on articles, participate in message boards, and submit images, photos, videos, or other content to the Services. We may ask you for additional information at other times, such as when you enter a contest or participate in a promotion, when you post an online ad, or when you order products from us or otherwise engage with the Services. 

**Information About Your Use of the Services.** In addition to the information you provide to us directly, we may collect information about your use of the Services. For example, we may collect: 

  * _Device information_ \- such as your hardware model, IP address, other unique device identifiers, operating system version, browser type and settings, such as language and available font settings, and settings of the device you use to access the Services. 
  * _Usage information_ \- such as information about the Services you use, the time and duration of your use of the Services and other information about your interaction with content offered through a Service, and any information stored using cookies, mobile ad identifiers, and similar technologies that we have set on your device. For detailed information about our use of cookies, web beacons, and other technologies, see the **Online Tracking and Advertising** section below. 
  * _Location information_ \- such as your computer's IP address, your mobile device's GPS signal or information about nearby Wi-Fi access points and cell towers that may be transmitted to us when you use certain Services. 

**Information From Third-Party Sources.** We may receive information about you from publicly and commercially available sources, as permitted by law, which we may combine with other information we receive from or about you. For example, we may receive information about you from a social media site if you connect to the Services through that site. 

**Other Information We Collect.** We also may collect other information about you, your device, or your use of the services in ways that we describe to you at the point of collection or otherwise with your consent. You may choose not to provide us with certain types of information but doing so may affect your ability to use some of the Services. 

We will never knowingly collect any personal information about children under the age of 13 (a "Minor"). The Website is not directed to Minors. If we obtain actual knowledge that we collected personal information about a Minor, that information will be automatically deleted from our database. Because we do not collect such information, we have no such information to use or to disclose to Third Parties. We have designed this policy in order to comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act ("COPPA"). You may read more about COPPA at [http://www.coppa.org](http://www.coppa.org/). If you become aware that your child, a Minor, has provided us with personal information without your consent, you should contact us immediately. 

**_How We Use Information_**

**To Provide and Manage the Services You Request.** This includes, for example, processing your subscriptions, sending you electronic newsletters, or enabling you to participate in the features provided by the Services. It also includes providing personalized content and recommendations to you, including by email. Through such features, we are able to bring you information and content tailored to your individual interests and needs. 

**To Contact You.** We may periodically contact you with offers and information about the Services and our affiliates, including in connection with your accounts, online surveys, legal notices, news stories, new features that you are entitled to access, and other important information. You may opt out of receiving commercial email messages from us by following the instructions contained in those email messages. 

**To Deliver Targeted Advertising.** We may use your information to facilitate the delivery of targeted ads, promotions, and offers to you, on behalf of ourselves and advertisers, on and off the Services. 

Please see the **Online Tracking and Advertising** section for further information about our and third parties' use of cookies, web beacons, mobile ad identifiers, and other tracking technologies to provide you relevant ads, as well as information about how to disable cookies and make other choices related to targeted advertising. 

**To Better Understand Our Users.** The Services may conduct research on our users' demographics, interests and behavior based on the information we collect. We do this to better understand and serve our users, and to improve our products and services. 

**To Protect the Rights of the Services and others.** We may use your personal information as we believe is necessary or appropriate to protect, enforce, or defend the legal rights, privacy, safety, or property of the Services, its employees or agents, or other users and to comply with applicable law. 

**Consent.** We may otherwise use your information with your consent or at your direction. 

**_Sharing of Information_**

The following provides information about entities with which we may share information. Our practices vary depending on the type of information. 

**Affiliates.** We may share information within our family of affiliated companies and other companies that might be of interest to you. 

**Business Partners.** We may also share your information with business partners to provide you with services that you request. For example, if you sign up for a promotion that runs on our Services but that is sponsored or co-sponsored by another company, your information may be shared with that sponsor. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of these entities. 

**Service Providers.** We may share information with vendors providing contractual services to us, such as hosting vendors, advertising service providers, and list managers. We also may share your information, including your payment information, as appropriate to process your payments for the Services or complete a transaction. 

**Other Parties When Required by Law or As Necessary to Protect Our Users and Services.** We may share your personal information as we believe is necessary or appropriate to protect, enforce, or defend the legal rights, privacy, safety, or property of the Services, our employees or agents or users or to comply with applicable law or legal process, including responding to requests from public and government authorities. 

**Logging In Through Social Media Services.** If you log into the Services with a social media service or if you connect a social media account with the Services, we may share your information with that social media service. The social media services' use of the shared information will be governed by the social media services' privacy policy and your social media account settings. If you do not want your information shared in this way, do not connect your social media service account with your Services. 

**Third Parties that Provide Content, Advertising, or Functionality.** When you use our Services, third parties may collect or receive certain information about you and/or your use of the Services ( _e.g._ , hashed data, click stream information, browser type, time and date, information about your interactions with advertisements and other content), including through the use of cookies, beacons, mobile ad identifiers, and similar technologies, in order to provide content, advertising, or functionality or to measure and analyze ad performance, on our Services or other websites or platforms. This information may be combined with information collected across different websites, online services, and other linked or associated devices. These third parties may use your information to improve their own services and consistent with their own privacy policies. 

**Other Parties in Connection With a Corporate Transaction.** We reserve the right to transfer any information we have about you in the event that we sell or transfer all or a portion of our business or assets to a third party, such as in the event of a merger, acquisition, or in connection with a bankruptcy reorganization. 

**Otherwise With Your Consent or At Your Direction.** In addition to the sharing described in this Privacy Policy, we may share information about you with third parties whenever you consent to or direct such sharing. We also may share other information with third parties in a manner that does not identify particular users, including, for example, aggregated data about how users are using our Services. 

**Disputes.** If you have any concerns or claims with respect to our data handling practices, please contact us first. We will investigate and attempt to resolve any complaints and disputes regarding our use and disclosure of your Individual Information. If your complaint or dispute cannot be resolved through our internal process, or if we do not adequately respond to your question, you agree to resolve your dispute through arbitration. If arbitration is necessary, it will be conducted by telephone and email, and if it must be done in person, it will be conducted in Denver, Colorado. The arbitration will be conducted by one arbitrator member of the American Arbitration Association, and under the rules of commercial arbitration of the American Arbitration Association or as agreed between you and the Company. Both parties will bear equally the cost of arbitration (exclusive of legal fees and expenses). You acknowledge and agree that you and the Company are each waiving the right to a trial by jury or to participate as a plaintiff or class member in any purported class action lawsuit, class-wide arbitration, private attorney-general action, or any other representative proceeding. Further, unless both you and the Company otherwise agree in writing, the arbitrator may not consolidate more than one person's claims and may not otherwise preside over any form of any class or representative proceeding. All decisions of the arbitrator will be final and binding on both parties and enforceable in any court of competent jurisdiction. For additional information you may contact [www.ADR.org](http://www.adr.org/). 

**Limitation of Liability.** We exercise reasonable efforts to safeguard the security and confidentiality of your personal information; however, transmissions protected by industry standard technology and administered by humans cannot be guaranteed to be secure. We will not be liable for unauthorized disclosure of personal information that occurs through no fault of our own including, but not limited to, errors in transmission, access to your account by anyone, uses of your Member ID and password by a third party, your failure to comply with your security obligations, and the unauthorized acts of our employees. ****

**Your California Privacy Rights.** (a) California residents are entitled once a year, free of charge, to request and obtain certain information regarding our disclosure, if any, of certain categories of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year. We do not share personal information with third parties for their own direct marketing purposes. (b) California residents who are registered users of the Services and are under the age of 18 are entitled, in accordance with California law, to request and obtain removal of content and information that they themselves post on the Services. You may request such removal by emailing us at [DPO@mediabreakaway.com](mailto:DPO@mediabreakaway.com). In your request, please provide a description of the material that you want removed and information reasonably sufficient to permit us to locate the material, and include your name, email address and/or website user name, year of birth, mailing address (including city, state, and zip code), and the subject line "California Removal Request" so that we can process your request. Please note that your request does not ensure complete or comprehensive removal of the material. For example, materials that you have posted may be republished or reposted by another user or third party. 

**

How to Contact us for NON-EEA and Switzerland Users. 

** You may reach us at [legal@mediabreakaway.com](mailto:legal@mediabreakaway.com). 

**For users in the EEA and Switzerland (where there is a discrepancy between the Privacy Policy for NON-EEA and Switzerland Users and EEA and Switzerland Users, the language in the NON-EAA provisions shall control)** : 

**_Embedded Content and Links to Third-Party Sites and Services_ **

Our Services may embed content from, or link to, third-party websites and services, including social media platforms, that are outside of our control. We are not responsible for the security or privacy of any information collected by other websites or other services. This Privacy Policy does not govern these third party's content or services, and we encourage you to review the privacy statements applicable to the third-party websites and services you use. 

**_How to Access or Update Your Information & Other Privacy Choices Available To You _ **

**Manage Your Account.** You may access or modify your account by contacting us at [DPO@mediabreakaway.com](mailto:DPO@mediabreakaway.com). This link will also allow you to update your subscriptions to electronic newsletters provided by the Services and to view your comment history. 

**Email Promotions.** You may opt out of receiving commercial email messages from us by following the instructions contained in those email messages. 

**Targeted Advertising.** You may choose whether to receive some forms of targeted advertising from many ad networks, audience segment providers, ad serving vendors. You may find more information on this topic by visiting websites operated by the _[ Network Advertising Initiative ](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) _ and _[Digital Advertising Alliance](http://www.aboutads.info/). _

If you would like to opt out of receiving targeted advertising from our network, please click the 'OPT OUT' button below.

If you use multiple devices and/or multiple browsers, you must opt out on each device/browser. You also must opt out again if you clear your cookies.

By opting out of targeted advertising on our network you will no longer receive targeted ads from our ad services, however you may still receive untargeted advertising. This opt out is only relevant for our ad serving products and will not have any effect on any 3rd party advertising services we may use.

**_Data Security_**

We have in place physical, electronic and managerial procedures to protect the information we collect online. However, as effective as these measures are, no security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our database, nor can we guarantee that the information you supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet. 

**_Other Important Information_**

**Children's Privacy.** We do not knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of 16 without parental consent, unless permitted by law. If we learn that a child under the age of 16 has provided us with personal information, we will delete it in accordance with applicable law. 

**Do-Not-Track Signals and Similar Mechanisms.** Some web browsers may transmit "do-not-track" signals to the websites with which the user communicates. Because of differences in how web browsers incorporate and activate this feature, it is not always clear whether users intend for these signals to be transmitted, or whether they even are aware of them. Because there currently is no industry standard concerning what, if anything, websites should do when they receive such signals, the Services currently do not take action in response to these signals. If and when a final standard is established and accepted, we will reassess how to respond to these signals. In the meantime, please see Online Tracking & Advertising for additional information about privacy choices that may be available to you with respect to targeted advertising. 

**International Transfers.** The Services are headquartered in the United States. Please be aware that if information you provide to us or that we obtain as a result of your use of the Services may be collected in your country and subsequently transferred to the United States or to another country in accordance with applicable law. By using the Services, you consent to the collection, international transfer, storage, and processing of your information 

**_Changes to Our Privacy Policy_**

We may modify this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of changes by posting changes here, or by other appropriate means. Any changes to the Privacy Policy will become effective when the updated policy is posted on the Services. Your use of the Services or your provision of personal information to use the Services following such changes indicates your acceptance of the revised Privacy Policy. 

**_Online Tracking & Advertising_**

**_How We Use Cookies, Web Beacons, and Similar Technologies and How To Disable These Technologies_ **

We and third parties that provide content, advertising, or functionality or measure and analyze ad performance on our Services, may use cookies, web beacons, mobile ad identifiers, and similar technologies to facilitate administration and navigation on the Site, to better understand and improve our Services, to determine and/or improve the advertising shown to you here or elsewhere, and to provide you with a customized online experience. 

**Cookies.** Cookies are small files that are placed on your computer when you visit a website. Cookies may be used to store a unique identification number tied to your computer or device so that you can be recognized as the same user across one or more browsing sessions, and across one or more sites. Cookies serve many useful purposes. For example: 

· Cookies can remember your sign-in credentials so you do not have to enter those credentials each time you visit a Service 

· Cookies can help us and third parties understand which parts of our Services are the most popular because they help us see which pages and features visitors access and how much time they spend on the pages. By studying this kind of information, we are better able to adapt our Services and provide you with a better experience. 

· Cookies help us and third parties understand which ads you have seen so that you don't receive the same ad each time you access a Service. 

Most browsers accept cookies automatically but can be configured not to do so or to notify the user when a cookie is being sent. If you wish to disable cookies, refer to your browser help menu to learn how to disable cookies. If you disable browser cookies or flash cookies, it may interfere with the proper functioning of the Services. 

**Beacons.** We, along with third parties, also may use technologies called beacons (or "pixels") that communicate information from your device to a server. Beacons can be embedded in online content, videos, and emails, and can allow a server to read certain types of information from your device, know when you have viewed particular content or a particular email message, determine the time and date on which you viewed the beacon, and the IP address of your device. We and third parties use beacons for a variety of purposes, including to analyze the use of our Services and (in conjunction with cookies) to provide content and ads that are more relevant to you. 

**Your IP Address.** We, along with third parties, may use your IP Address to determine your location, ISP ("Internet Service Provider"), and internet connection type. We may use this information for ad targeting as well as to protect our network from fraudulent activity. 

**HTTP Headers.** We, along with third parties, may use the HTTP Headers provided by your device/web browser in order to determine what web browser you are using, the operating system you are using, your preferred language, and if you are accessing our services behind a proxy. We may use this information for ad targeting as well as to protect our network from fraudulent activity. 

**Local Storage & Other Tracking Technologies. ** We, along with third parties, may use other kinds of technologies, such as Local Shared Objects (also referred to as "Flash cookies") and HTML5 local storage, in connection with our Services. We also may use unique identifiers associated with your device, such as mobile ad identifiers. These technologies are similar to the cookies discussed above in that they are stored on your device and can be used to store certain information about your activities and preferences. However, these technologies may make use of different parts of your device from standard cookies, and so you might not be able to control them using standard browser tools and settings. For HTML5 local storage, the method for disabling HTML5 will vary depending on your browser. For Flash cookies, information about disabling or deleting information contained in Flash cookies can be found _[ here ](http://helpx.adobe.com/flash-player/kb/disable-local-shared-objects-flash.html) _ . 

**_Additional Choices With Respect To Targeted Advertising_ **

As described above, we and third parties may use cookies and other tracking technologies to facilitate serving relevant ads to you. For example, these technologies help us determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before, tailor ads to you if you have visited our site before and avoid sending you duplicate advertisements. You can learn more about certain types of targeted advertising by visiting the _[Digital Advertising Alliance ](http://www.aboutads.info/) _ website. 

Due to differences between using apps and websites on mobile devices, you may need to take additional steps to disable tracking technologies in mobile apps. Many mobile devices allow you to opt-out of targeted advertising for mobile apps using the settings within the mobile app or your mobile device. For more information, please check your mobile settings. You also may uninstall our apps using the standard uninstall process available on your mobile device or app marketplace. 

**Users in the EEA and Switzerland**

If you are a user in the EEA or Switzerland. the following information applies with respect to personal data collected through your use of our Services. 

**Purposes of processing and legal basis for processing.** We process personal data consistent with our disclosures in this Privacy Policy. We process personal data on the following legal bases: (1) with your consent; (2) as necessary to perform our agreement to provide Services to you; and (3) as necessary for our legitimate interests in providing the Services where those interests do not override your fundamental rights and freedoms related to data privacy. 

**Transfers.** Personal data we collect may be transferred to, and stored and processed in, the United States or any other country in which we or our affiliates or processors maintain facilities. We will ensure that transfers of personal data to a third country or an international organization are subject to appropriate safeguards. 

**Individual Rights.** If you are a resident of the EEA or Switzerland, you have certain rights under Chapter 3 of the EU General Data Protection Regulation. To make a request or otherwise exercise your rights under Chapter 3, you can contact us at [DPO@mediabreakaway.com](mailto:DPO@mediabreakaway.com). In order to respond to your request, we will need to verify your identity and residency and may require you to provide us with supporting information. 

**For More Information** . Please contact us at [DPO@mediabreakaway.com](mailto:DPO@mediabreakaway.com) or for our EU Representative, please contact us at [EURepresentative@mediabreakaway.com](mailto:EURepresentative@mediabreakaway.com)
